http://www.caspercollege.edu/about/privacy-policy

ULoginPrivacy Policy Section NavigationAbout Casper CollegeAbout Casper CollegeAcademic CalendarAccreditationEvents CalendarGovernanceJobs at Casper CollegeMap and DirectionsMissionOffice of the PresidentPolicies and ProceduresPrivacy PolicyStudent Consumer InformationWeather/Closure InformationCasper College is committed to protecting your privacy. By using this website, you are consenting to our collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Statement.This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for Casper College websites and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Statement, unless otherwise noted, all references to “Casper College” or “the College” include caspercollege.edu, tbirds.cc, caspercollegearts.cc, casper.universitytickets.com, and useast.radiusbycampusmgmt.com.The privacy of visitors to our website is very important to Casper College. The College has adopted this policy to inform visitors about the College’s data collection practices — both when a visitor voluntarily enters and transmits information to the College and when data are collected automatically by systems used by Casper College.This page describes what information is gathered, how this information is processed, as well as the choices that are available to you regarding the use of the information you provide.What information do we gather about you?Our policy is to not collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit our websites unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. However, our website does automatically recognize some anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Casper College. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by the College for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Casper College website. We connect data from different systems but do not link IP addresses to any personal information. We may also collect other information as described in this policy.What do we use your information for?We use the information we gather from you for systems administration purposes, abuse prevention, to track user trends, and for the other purposed described in this policy. If you send us an email, the email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests for information.User information may be shared with third-party vendors to the extent necessary to provide and improve web services or other communications to users. For example, we use third parties such as Google Analytics and Siteimprove to generate reports on site usage, web traffic, user behavior, and user interests in order to optimize our website for our visitors. We also use geographic, demographic, and interest-based reports of our website visitors to create custom audience lists. Casper College may use information collected to serve targeted advertising to you if you are added to a custom audience list. If a retargeting ad is served to you, this means that you may see Casper College advertised on other websites you visit. We prohibit any third parties who receive user information for this purpose from using or sharing user information for any purpose other than providing services for the benefit of our users. We may also use cookies from our advertising partners for the purposes described in this policy.Names, postal and email addresses, and phone numbers provided by visitors via online forms may added to the Colleges database(s). This information may be used for correspondence or other uses consistent with Casper College’s business practices and/or academic mission. Casper College may also use such information to provide users with information concerning College events and other College community activities and services.Casper College websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Casper College or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Casper College; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Casper College, or the public.How is this information collected and how can you opt out?A cookie is a small data file that is written to your hard drive that contains information about your visit to a web page. Personally identifiable information is not stored in these cookies. First Party Cookies are set through Casper College websites directly, including the Google Analytics cookie. Third Party Cookies are set by third parties, also through Casper College websites.An anonymous identifier is a random string of characters that is used for the same purposes as a cookie on platforms, including certain mobile devices, where cookie technology is not available.If you prefer not to receive cookies, you may configure your browser not to accept them at all, or to notify and require approval before accepting new cookies. Some web pages/sites may not function properly if the cookies are turned off, or you may have to provide the same information each time you visit those pages.Disabling Cookies and/or Opting Out of Advertising FeaturesYou may disable cookies through your individual browser options or use a browser plugin to opt-out. If you would like to learn more about cookies please refer to the following website: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.Please visit the following pages for more information on Google Analytics terms of use, Google’s privacy practices, and ad settings.Users can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by using Google Ads Settings. For more information, please visit Google’s Privacy Policy.Google is one of many ad networks which personalize ads based on your activity online. Go to AdChoices to control ads from other ad networks. You can also use the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) tool, which will allow you to opt out of seeing personalized ads from other NAI approved member companies: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/External linksSome Casper College websites may contain links to external websites for your convenience that are not owned by, or officially affiliated with, Casper College in any way. Casper College is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.Information protectionTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information we gather about you, we have taken commercially reasonable steps to protect the information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.Users Located in the European Economic AreaCasper College abides by the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) that impacts individuals within the European Union and the European Economic Area. For more information on these data privacy provisions please contact Enrollment Services.DisclaimerThe information provided in this policy statement should not be construed as giving business, legal or other advice, or as guaranteeing the security of information through Casper College’s websites.We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.Contact informationIf you have questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this website, you may contact:Casper CollegePublic Relations Departmentpr@caspercollege.eduAbout Casper CollegeAbout Casper CollegeAcademic CalendarAccreditationEvents CalendarGovernanceJobs at Casper CollegeMap and DirectionsMissionOffice of the PresidentPolicies and ProceduresPrivacy PolicyStudent Consumer InformationWeather/Closure InformationNext StepsVisit Casper CollegeRequest InformationApply for AdmissionJust for YouFuture StudentsCurrent StudentsWork at CCFaculty and StaffCommunity ResourcesAlumni and FriendsHelpful QuicklinksA-Z GuideEmployee DirectoryOffices and ServicesAcademic CalendarAccessibilityBookstoreCampus MapCC Alerts/SafetyEvents CalendarGive to CC FoundationJobs at Casper CollegeNews: Inside CCStudent Success CenterCasper College125 College DriveCasper, WY 82601307-268-2100 Contact UsEmergency Information Alert  |  Report an Incident or Concern  |  Nondiscrimination  |  Privacy Policy  |  Mission  |  DirectionsFollowFollowFollowFollowFollow
